So that Hazamada guy really said
he knows zilch about the
the super-charged sonuvabitch
who killed my bro?
Yeah.
He said he's only ever
talked to him over the phone.
And you believed him, Josuke?
You tortured the bastard, right?
Look, if Hazamada really
knew who the user is,
he would've been
totally snuffed out by now.
I guess you're right…
Just like my bro.
Yeah.
That Hazamada's still breathing
is proof enough he's telling the truth.
But Hazamada also had this to say…
For whatever reason, whether
or not they know each other,
Stand users are inadvertently
drawn to each other.
You know the myth that
says the red thread of fate
connects you with
your partner-to-be, right?
Well, it's like that.
Someday, in some place,
they'll cross paths.
The user could be
an enemy, a friend,
the guy stepping on your foot
on the bus,
or your new next-door neighbor.
Nobody knows.
Morioh's a small town, you know…
Who knows how many
Stand users it has.
But try as they may to hide,
they'll eventually emerge.
He knows it's inevitable.
He wants you to disappear.
Dammit.
He's a damn coward!
What the hell is he waiting for?!
It just means he's playing it safe.
When guys like that decide to attack,
it's because they
know there's no way they can lose.
Oh?
Hey, that's Koichi.
What's he doing posing
in some snooty cafe?
Hey, Ko—
What?!
A… A girl?!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 8
YUKAKO YAMAGISHI
FALLS IN LOVE, PART 1
Koichi, I hope meeting me here…
wasn't too much…
of a nuisance.
Huh? No, it wasn't a nuisance at all…
I did kinda wonder
what this was all about.
Wow, Koichi with a girl…
That's Yukako Yamagishi
from my class.
Come on! Let's get a closer look!
If you want me to show you
my homework,
I have to tell you my grades
aren't that good,
and my handwriting's kinda messy.
If it's money you need, I could
probably give you 'bout 1,000 yen…
Or do you want me to
be the weekly class leader?
No, I don't want any of those things.
Huh? You don't?
Then what is it?
If you need someone to take
in a kitten or a puppy,
sorry to say I already
have a dopey dog named Police.
Koichi!
I have to tell you something.
Koichi…
I…
Koichi, I love you!
Huh?
What'd she say?!
U-Um… Uh, um…
Wh-What was that?!
All day, you're all
I think about, Koichi.
I've been so frightened
to utter those words to you…
I couldn't hold it in anymore.
My heart was going to burst.
I understand if you hate me.
I had to take the leap and tell you.
Is this really happening?
Is she professing her love…
to me?!
I wouldn't believe it if I hadn't heard it.
That's what she said, right?
I-I'm so happy…
Why Koichi?
This can't be happening!
There's no way!
No one's ever said that to me!
Come on, there's no need to cry!
But holy crap…
That Koichi is something…
Koichi, you must have
a girlfriend already…
Huh? No, actually I don't…
But, well…
You wouldn't be teasing me would—
I'm dead serious!
Koichi, I noticed recently your face
has become more chiseled.
A strong face with
courage and conviction…
Then I see that smile…
And you become so charming.
Hmm, I see what's she's saying.
I have a chiseled face too, don't I?
What attracts me most
to a man is his potential.
And Koichi, you're brimming with it!
Wow, no one's ever said that to me…
But you must hate
homely girls like me, though.
Huh? Homely? That's not it at all…
Dammit, she's hot!
Just go out with her already!
That bastard has all the luck!
Do you hate me?
Huh?
Uh, no that's not it at all…
Do you love me?
Huh? Wait a sec…
It's just that, um…
You do hate me…
Huh? No, not at all!
It's just, you caught me
off guard when you—
Which is it?!
Do you love me or not?!
Answer me, dammit!
I already poured my heart out to you!
And now I spilled my coffee!
This is all because of you!
I… I'm so sorry…
I don't know what came over me.
Well, you will come
see me again, won't you?
I… I suddenly feel
like a deflated balloon.
That totally got rid of
any jealousy I had.
Y-Yeah…
Let's pretend we didn't see that.
Yeah.
What's with my cola?!
What's all this hair in it?!
Stand users are drawn to each other…
It couldn't be…
CHEMISTRY LAB
It's me, Koichi.
Y-Yukako!
Whatcha doing?
Um, well, as you can see,
it's my turn to clean the lab.
Fourth period was chemistry lab.
Ah…
Koichi…
I know I said
some strange things yesterday.
You'll forget all that, won't you?
I always get that way
when I overthink things.
I'm so embarrassed.
I suppose it's always
important to be open minded.
Uh, r-right…
You surprised me a little,
b-but I didn't think anything of it…
We can still be friends, right?
Yes, of course! I'd like that!
Oh, thank goodness!
I was so worried you hated me!
I was tossing and turning all night.
You were just overreacting.
And as a little something
to show you I'm sorry… Here.
I spent all night
knitting this for you, Koichi.
I'm so relieved! It fits perfectly!
I knew the length and chest width, but
I had know idea about the shoulders.
CHARM
I made you an amulet, too…
Now you can find true love.
I also made us a couple of bento boxes
so we can have lunch together…
I bought this shrimp
this morning at the local market.
You can't find this freshness
at a grocery store.
And this is flounder meuniere.
I made sure to remove
every single bone with tweezers.
Now, say, "Ah."
Ahh…
I know one thing's for sure…
Yukako Yamagishi is
completely deranged!
Ahh…
I've gotta put a stop to this now!
B-But if I take a bite,
I'll just validate her feelings…
And if I refuse, she'll kill me!
What am I gonna do?!
Hirose!
Quit slacking off!
Hurry up and dump
this garbage before class starts.
Thank god!
Of course! Of course!
I better go throw it away.
Ugh, you're hopeless.
Here, give me that.
I'll take the other side.
Huh? N-No, you don't have to…
Just hand it over!
I'm the class rep, so I'll be
the one getting yelled at.
- Jeez!
- S-Sorry…
Hey, you.
Would you mind
stop flirting with Koichi?
Koichi? You mean Koichi Hirose?
I don't have the foggiest idea
what you're talking about.
I know exactly
what you're trying to pull.
I can smell homewrecker
all over you!
Home-what?!
What the hell are you talking about?
Listen carefully.
If I ever catch you trying
to seduce Koichi again,
I'll make your perfect
little life a living hell.
Not so fast, bitch.
I was trying to take the high road.
This is all about Koichi Hirose?
I couldn't give two shits about him!
You can't tell me
what I can or can't do!
Dumbass!
Ow!
What was that?
What the hell is her problem?!
She's out of her mind.
She has the hots for Hirose?
Hmph. Don't make me laugh.
The entire school'll hear about this!
Huh?
What is that?
I feel something hot…
Something's not right.
Something's really not right…
This is crazy hot…
W-Water!
S-Someone! I need w-wa…
Hey, Josuke…
Looks like Yukako Yamagishi
really is a Stand user.
A Stand that manipulates hair at will.
Yeah.
But it doesn't look like she'd attack
Koichi or us for that matter.
So, Okuyasu, what are you
gonna do about her hair?
I can't fix stuff the Hand takes away.
I think I've done enough!
I kept her from getting burnt
to a crisp, didn't I?
Sorry to disappoint,
I'm not much of a stylist.
REVERB
KOICHI HIROSE
What am I gonna do?
YEAR 1
ENGLISH EXAM ANSWER SHEET
QUIZ 2 KOICHI HIROSE
Look what I got
on my latest English test.
Yukako is stressing me
out so much, I can't concentrate.
Even I did better!
My score was only 32, though.
You know, to be totally honest,
I was a little excited at first.
No girl's ever said
she loved me before.
I know. Believe me, I know!
All too well!
I was too wishy-washy
and brought all this on myself!
I'll do it!
That's what I'm gonna tell her!
I'm not interested,
so leave me alone!
I'd think twice about that, Koichi.
You're only going to fan
the flames of Yukako's passion.
She'll lose it again.
I guess you're right.
Of course I'm right.
Now listen.
Convincing Yukako Yamagishi to stop
using her hair for evil can wait.
Right now,
we've gotta figure out a way
to not directly provoke her to anger.
But how?
Look, no matter how infatuated
she is with you,
if she comes to
her own conclusion that
you're the most pathetic, grossest,
schmuck around,
then everyone lives
happily ever after, right?
Y-Yeah…
So all you've got to
do is act that way in front of her.
I get it! That'll work!
You're so smart, Josuke.
Well thank you!
Not sure how much of
a compliment it is coming from you.
What could I do to make
Yukako think I'm totally unappealing?
Well, mama's boys and gross guys
are usually major turn offs.
I can't make her think
I'm a mama's boy!
Then she'll hate my mom
and go after her!
That settles it.
You'll be the gross guy!
No more baths from now on.
Huh?!
Yeah, and no teeth brushing
or changing your underwear.
How about raising some lice
or spiders in your hair?
Yeah but stinky socks are pretty gross.
Just fart all over the place.
She'll think you're foul!
This isn't a joke! I'm serious!
I am being serious!
You gotta have snot and drool, too!
What?!
If you don't like that,
then it looks like your only option is to
become a spineless nobody
with no prospects.
You need to make her
lose all interest.
We'll do it together, okay?
Okay…
What? Koichi Hirose did what?
I don't believe it!
He was really shoplifting?
Disgusting.
Yeah! Koichi said it himself.
To think he was bragging
about it, the jerk!
Even worse, Koichi can't
keep a promise to save his life!
I lent him money,
and the ass never paid me back.
He also cheats on tests
and steals girls' underwear.
The guy's got no future.
He'll end up ruining his own life.
No way am I gonna
hang out with him anymore.
Our friendship is over!
Man, that is one intense chick.
Now if Koichi can just confirm
all the stuff we said tomorrow,
there's no way
she'll still be interested.
Josuke, Okuyasu…
I wonder if all that stuff
they did worked.
I hope she just forgets about me.
What is that?
My eyes are closed..
Must be a dream.
A woman?
I-It's Yukako!
Ah, darn it!
She's even corrupting
my dreams now.
Can't she just give me a rest?!
Koichi, your friends don't
seem to think very highly of you.
Don't worry. I'm here for you.
I'll educate you
and turn you into the epitome of
what it means to be a man.
You have a certain something
other men don't.
And you must live up to that potential.
J- Josuke! It all backfired!
What is this place?
Koichi, are you hungry?
Breakfast is almost ready.
O-Okay…
She's got that hair Stand..
I can't resist.
I've got to find an opening and run.
That's my only hope!
I-I'm curious…
Yes?
Your hair last night…
Wh-What was that?
Were you surprised?
Silly me. I guess the first time
would startle anyone.
It was around February this year,
that someone shot an arrow
into my chest.
Though, I was probably dreaming.
When I woke up, my wound
was gone, and I had my power…
Keicho Nijimura!
D-Do you know anyone else who
has powers like that?
No, I don't.
She doesn't know I'm a Stand user!
Now, sit down.
You are a growing boy.
If you don't eat well,
you'll never become
my outstanding little man.
I-I've gotta play along for now
This looks amazing!
Oh boy!
Not so fast, Koichi!
ENGLISH EXAM ANSWER SHEET
KOICHI HIROSE
You received a 16
on your English test.
There may be more to a man
than his intelligence,
but this is unforgivable.
You're going to study while you eat.
Okay?
Now for some questions.
Select the best answer from
among boxes A, B, and C.
The box you choose
holds your next meal.
W-Wait a sec…
You'll do what I say!
While you're in this house,
life must revolve around
your betterment!
Right?
Now for the question.
Prince is known to use the words
"funky music" in his lyrics.
What is the best
Japanese translation?
JUBILANT MUSIC
A: Nekkyo no ongaku
B: Genshi no ongaku
PRIMORDIAL MUSIC
C: Gensou no ongaku.
ILLUSIONARY MUSIC
I-If I don't answer,
she'll get hysterical…
B-But I have no clue!
I have a hunch it's A,
but it could easily be B or C.
Screw it! I can do this…
My guess is…
B…
You got it!
Hurray!
You won hard-boiled eggs!
I'll peel them for you.
With a pinch of salt, right?
By the way, if you had chosen A,
you would've had to eat this eraser.
JUBILANT MUSIC
Huh?!
Box C would've been soap.
W-What?!
Next on the menu is bacon and eggs.
Good luck!
Your question is…
Which characters express
"contrast" in Japanese?
Would it be taisho A,
taisho B, or taisho C?
TAISHO
Would it be taisho A,
taisho B, or taisho C?
TAISHO
Sh-She's not playing…
If I choose the wrong box,
she'll force me to eat
its contents for sure…
Come now, enough dilly dallying!
Your food will get cold.
U-Um, uh…
What can I do?
Now she's playing hardball…
I-I think it's C…
Koichi, you were watching
my expression just now, weren't you?
Huh?!
So your reputation for being
a sneaking, shoplifting cheat is true!
For your penalty,
you shall consume
the contents of boxes A and B.
A is English vocab corn flakes.
B is asparagus a Ia English dictionary.
You're going to learn with
every bite you take!
Here!
Open that mouth!
I'm gonna feed you.
What's wrong? Eat, damn it!
That's it!
You expect me to sit back
and take this?
Well I can't take it any more!
I'm getting outta here!
Something's pulling me!
It's got my scalp!
Th-There's some kind of
hair moving around in mine!
That's right. I implanted a few hundred
strands of my own hair into your scalp.
Koichi,
you will probably hate me for this.
But by the time you leave this house,
you'll look in the mirror
and see a new man,
and you will most certainly thank me.
You'll realize you need
a woman like me in your life.
You won't be able to live
without Yukako Yamagishi.
Should you care to know,
until you finish your plates,
I will not be distributing
any more food.
This is the vacation home
of a famous CEO.
No one will visit until summer.
S-Summer?!
And even then,
it doesn't matter who may come…
Love is invincible, you know.
H-Help!
EPISODE 9
YUKAKO YAMAGISHI
FALLS IN LOVE, PART 2